{
    "id": "64a3855289cb40db8ee2f702b1210539",
    "title": "Much And Many",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I haven’t got …………………. time.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "much",
                "many"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "54e0a6a542864a4e84794fdeb72f3311"
        },
        {
            "question": "How ……………….. the roof needs repairing?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "much",
                "much of",
                "many",
                "many of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "cdf53353b2a9495d914e8e64db5be054"
        },
        {
            "question": "You can have as ……………….. chocolates as you want.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "many",
                "many of",
                "much"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c1bfd668bb6f41248ab474e0781c108b"
        },
        {
            "question": "You can stay for as ………………… days as you want.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "many",
                "much"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "09bf33fb45514d579f1fe7116216df43"
        },
        {
            "question": "There aren’t ………………… large eggs left.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "many",
                "much"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "bcf4747747f74ed5a01a31720bafa5a5"
        },
        {
            "question": "You won’t be able to see ……………….. a country in a week.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "much",
                "much of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "76dd477c87f64bdc867a505792616989"
        },
        {
            "question": "If you skip too ……………….. your classes, you won’t pass the exam.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "many",
                "many of",
                "much",
                "much of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f30b3a5001214561b014aaaf7a1df707"
        },
        {
            "question": "How …………………. you will be there?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "many",
                "many of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c9d2cad9381943e18423027d9fa4fc5d"
        },
        {
            "question": "You didn’t eat …………………. breakfast.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "many",
                "much"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "40134fd8f7994a83b726f7a5f117c484"
        },
        {
            "question": "There was so ………………… traffic that it took me two hours to get to work.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "much",
                "many"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4ac01aaec99448eb9402089661a8de57"
        }
    ]
}